http://www.crystalmeth.org/home/privacy-policy.html

Press to Call - Helpline: 1-(855) 638-4373
Website Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our Store site, place an order or fill out a form. When ordering on our Store website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order in the Store.
The Store offers the use of a secure server when placing orders of products. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We also use cookies to help our Geo auto coder find your location for the purposes of displaying meeting maps only. We do not store this data.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our Store website may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Store website at: http://cma-online-store2.mybigcommerce.com/condition-of-use/
Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Crystal Meth Anonymous, Inc4470 W Sunset Blvd Ste 107 PMB 555Los Angeles , CA 90027-6302USA
HomeIs CMA for Me?Privacy PolicyThe PublicFor Friends and FamiliesFor the Professional
Requesting AssistanceLearn About Hospital & InstitutionsFor The MediaAnonymity and the MediaCMAs History of ServiceThe FellowshipCMA LiteratureThe CMA BookVoices of the Fellowship ®Voices BlogSpeaker RecordingsGroup ResourcesMake a Seventh Tradition ContributionMember Donation to CMAGroup Donation to CMAService in CMAOrder Chips, Medallions and BooksAdvisory CommitteesCommunications Advisory CommitteeCMA Service PortalFinance Advisory CommitteeContributions by RegionQuarterly Profit & Loss ReportGeneral Service Conference Advisory CommitteeHospitals & Institutions Advisory CommitteeH&I Literature & DocumentsSubmit Your Story to H&ILiterature Advisory CommitteeLiterature Advisory Committee -- ContributionsSubmit Your StoryMeditation Reader ContributionsPublic Information & Outreach Advisory CommitteeGeneral Service ConferenceMeetingsOnline CMA MeetingsCMA Meeting MapCMA Meeting SearchCMA Meeting DirectoryList or Modify Your MeetingAdd A MeetingChange/Update A CMA MeetingDelete A CMA MeetingStart a MeetingMeeting ReadingsMeeting FormatsContributeContactHELP - CLICK HERE FOR HELPLocal ContactsLocal Group RegistrarsGeneral Services Contacts
